interactiveachievement.net 2015-12-05

# Privacy Policy: Interactive Achievement

#### Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy applies to [www.interactiveachievement.com](http://interactiveachievement.com/) owned and operated by Interactive Achievement, LLC. This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Interactive Achievement collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the www.interactiveachievement.com website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Interactive Achievement. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal identification information and how you can access and update this information. Interactive Achievement, LLC. has received TRUSTe’s Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and our practices have been reviewed for compliance with the TRUSTe program viewable on the validation page available by clicking on the TRUSTe seal. The TRUSTe certification covers only our collection, use and disclosure of information we collect through our website: [http://interactiveachievement.com](http://interactiveachievement.com/), our service: [https://ontrac.interactiveachievement.net](https://ontrac.interactiveachievement.net/) and our mobile application. The use of information collected through our service shall be limited to the purpose of providing the service for which the Client has engaged Interactive Achievement, LLC. If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact [TRUSTe here](https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request). Interactive Achievement, LLC. complies with the U.S. – E.U. Safe Harbor framework and the U.S. – Swiss Safe Harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal data from European Union member countries and Switzerland. Interactive Achievement, LLC. has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view Interactive Achievement’s certification, please visit <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>

#### Personal identification information

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, subscribe to the newsletter, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, phone number. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

#### Information Related to Data Collected through the OnTRAC Service

Interactive Achievement, LLC. collects information under the direction of its Clients, and has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes. If you are a customer of one of our Clients and would no longer like to be contacted by one of our Clients that use our service, please contact the Client that you interact with directly. We may transfer personal information to companies that help us provide our service. Transfers to subsequent third parties are covered by the service agreements with our Clients.

#### Access and Retention of Data Controlled by our Clients:

Interactive Achievement, LLC. has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal information it processes. An individual who seeks access, or who seeks to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data should direct his query to Interactive Achievement, LLC’s Client (the data controller). If you requested to remove data we will respond within 30 days. We will retain personal information we process on behalf of our Clients for as long as needed to provide services to our Client. Interactive Achievement, LLC. will retain this personal information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

#### Mobile Application

When you download and use our Services, we automatically collect information on the type of device you use, and operating system version.

#### Geo-Location Data

We do not ask you for, access or track any location based information from your mobile device at anytime while downloading or using our Mobile App or Service.

#### Mobile Analytics

We use mobile analytics software to allow us to better understand the functionality of our Mobile Software on your phone. This software may record information such us how often you use the application, the events that occur within the application, aggregated usage, performance data, and where the application was downloaded from. We do not link the information we store within the analytics software to any personal information you submit within the mobile app.

#### Tracking Technologies

Technologies such as: cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by Interactive Achievement, LLC. and our content and statistics partners, affiliates, analytics, and customer service providers. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis. We use cookies for user experience and authentication. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited.

#### Log Files

As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data. We do not link this automatically collected data to other information we collect about you.

#### Local Storage Objects

We use Local Storage Objects such as HTML5 to store [content information and preferences.] Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site or to display advertising based upon your web browsing activity to use LSOs such as HTML5 to collect and store information. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5 LSOs.

#### Behavioral Targeting / Re-Targeting

We partner with a third party to either display advertising on our website or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partner may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this site and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by clicking [here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/) (or if located in the European Union click [here](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/).) Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads. You will continue to receive generic ads. 

**How we use collected information**

Interactive Achievement may collect and use Users personal identification information for the following purposes:

  1. To run a promotion, contest, survey or other Site feature
  2. To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.
  3. To send periodic emails

We may use the email address to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email. The user may also access the email preferences in their account settings page [here](http://info2.interactiveachievement.com/UnsubscribePage.html) or [contact us](http://interactiveachievement.com/connect/contact/) via our website.

#### How we protect your information

The security of your personal identification information is important to us. We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal identification information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

#### Sharing your personal identification information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.

#### Legal Disclaimer

We may also disclose your personal identification information as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process and when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request. If Interactive Achievement, LLC. is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our website of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.

#### User Access and Choice

If your personal information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may [correct, update, amend, delete/remove, ask to have it removed from a public forum, directory or testimonial on our site or deactivate it] by making the change on our member information page or by emailing our customer support at support@interactiveachievement.com or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below. We will respond to your request to access within 30 days. We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

#### Third party websites

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

#### Blog

Our website offers publicly accessible blogs. Our blog is managed by a third party application called Disqus and they may require you to register to post a comment. We do not have access or control of the information posted to the blog. You will need to contact or login into the third party application if you want the personal identification information that was posted to the comments section removed. To learn how the third party application uses your information, please review Disqus [privacy policy](https://help.disqus.com/customer/portal/articles/466259-privacy-policy).

#### Testimonials

We display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our website in addition to other endorsements. With your consent, we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at [privacy@interactiveachievement.com](mailto:privacy@interactiveachievement.com).

#### Social Media Widgets

Our website includes Social Media Features, such as Facebook Like button [and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site]. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our website. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

#### Changes to this privacy policy

Interactive Achievement, LLC has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time to reflect any changes to our information practices. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page and we will notify you by email (sent to the email address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal identification information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

#### Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

#### Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:

Interactive Achievement  
601 Campbell Ave SW, Roanoke VA 24016  
Phone: 866-305-8460  

This document was last updated on June 8, 2015.
